<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My blogging site</title>
    <link>https://portfolio.mehsen.website/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My blogging site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright><atom:link href="https://portfolio.mehsen.website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://portfolio.mehsen.website/posts/github/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://portfolio.mehsen.website/posts/github/</guid>
      <description>What do I use my Github for? Boring stuff out of the way Like any other tech student I of course use it to host my school projects, wether I need to collaborate with others or work on my own having everything on Github is quite handy
The cool stuff Before I can get into it first some context. I use Linux as my daily operating system, I use it for everything (work, school, gaming, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://portfolio.mehsen.website/posts/krashosting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://portfolio.mehsen.website/posts/krashosting/</guid>
      <description>Krashosting What is this Krashosting is a school project that I made with my a group of my classmates at school. The goal of the project was to make a website for a hosting company to sell packages and be able to create/edit/delete packages.
But the but is that we sadly the admin dashboard was kinda done in a hurry so I can only show the frontend.
What was my role The project was worked on by 3 people, including me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://portfolio.mehsen.website/posts/monitor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://portfolio.mehsen.website/posts/monitor/</guid>
      <description>Server RAM monitor Why RAM monitor though? well&amp;hellip;. it was suppossed to be a full system monitor but I ran out of time. The whole idea of this project started because I wanted to learn about websockets and a bit of Typescript.
Websockets? Yeah! how else are you going to keep getting update from a server? sending a request every couple seconds or so is really not effecient, so websockets was my go to.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
